菲尔
Hey, Phil.
杰 你在哪 正在做什么
Jay, where are you? What are you doing?
我正要进我家门
I'm just walking into my house.
停下 一步都别往前走了
Stop! Don't you take another step!
你在说什么疯话
What the hell are you talking about?
克莱尔刚告诉我你为歌洛莉亚
Claire just told me your Valentine's
准备的情人节计划
plans for Gloria.
你这么进家门就死定了
You're walking into a buzz saw!
上车
Get in.
你们这是什么扮相
What am I looking at here?
-没什么 -是我们的情人节角色扮演
- Nothing. - Oh, it's a role-playing thing we do on Valentine's.
-让滚床单更有激情 -不说能死吗菲尔
- It bumps the lovemaking up a notch. - ?Phil, why?
歌洛莉亚在生你的气
Gloria is mad at you.
如果你拿着应付了事的礼物进屋
If you walk in there with some lame gift,
她会要了你的命的 先生
she will bite your head right off, mister.
你这是瞎操心
Well, you worried for nothing.
我给她买了块精致的饼干
I bought her a nice cookie,
还有超市卖的最大的聚纤气球
and the biggest Mylar balloon they sold at the grocery store.
醒醒吧老头 你要失去她了
Wake up, man! You're losing her!
你什么时候和歌洛莉亚聊过
When did you talk to Gloria?
今天下午
This afternoon.
我要带克莱尔去穆赫兰道的眺望塔
I'm just taking Claire up to the overlook on Mulholland
在那里来一段老派亲热
for a little old-school make-out sesh.
菲尔
Oh, Phil.
你真会过情人节
You're so good at Valentine things...
不像某个不知感恩的自私鬼
unlike some ungrateful, selfish men
一点都不知道珍惜女人
that don't appreciate women!
-你今晚得多花点心思 -怎么做
- You need to step it up tonight. - How?
像怪胎一样玩角色扮演吗
By dressing up in costumes like weirdos?
这并不怪 爸 挺好玩的
It's not weird, Dad. It's fun.
是的 今晚我们得以重返十七岁
Yeah. Tonight, we get to be 17 again,
当时我们都还是纯洁天真的处子
when we were just a couple of innocent, wide-eyed virgins.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我才不要
I'm not doing it.
今天歌洛莉亚知道我们的计划时说
Today, when Gloria found out what we were doing, she said,
"该死的 菲尔 你真会过情人节
"Damn it, Phil. You are so good at Valentine's.
我真希望杰和你一样性感"
I wish Jay was as sexy as you."
她从没说过那种话
She never said that.
大概就是这意思了
I'm paraphrasing.
好吧 打给歌洛莉亚
Okay, call Gloria,
告诉她去酒店酒吧等你
tell her to meet you at a hotel bar,
然后你扮成某个浪漫角色现身
and then you show up as some romantic character.
-我能扮成谁 -谁都行
- Who would I be? - Anybody.
一个你能想到的最具异域风情的人
Think of the most exotic person you can.
艾森豪威尔将军
General Eisenhower,
美国高速公路之父
the father of the American freeway.
得想个比这更性感些的人
You're gonna want to think a little sexier than that.
你们看的那些照片都照得不好
You have not seen the right photos.
你怎么吃上了 他不是要带你出去吃晚餐吗
What are you doing? I thought he was taking you out to dinner.
我先吃点免得到时像猪一样能吃
I'm pre-eating so I don't look like a pig.
求你告诉我你去约会时不会大吃特吃
Oh, please tell me you don't eat on dates.
哪个男人这么幸运
Who's the lucky guy?
是艾丽克斯大学的一个教授
Oh, this professor from Alex's college.
通常我不和那种男人约会
Normally, I wouldn't go out with a guy like that,
但他有点特别的魅力
but there's something about him.
"有点特别的魅力"
"Something about him"?
他可是天才
He's a genius.
他是我们大学最受敬仰的学者之一
He's one of the most respected minds on campus,
还刚好长得像简·奥斯汀小说里写的
who also happens to look like the protagonist
一个男主角
from a Jane Austen novel.
你完全配不上他
He's totally out of your league.
现在你说的可是疯话了
Oh, well, now you're being crazy.
你喜欢他还是怎么的
Are you into him or something?
不 我是真的担心
No! I'm just genuinely concerned
你会让自己或我丢人
you're going to embarrass yourself or me.
至少查一查占星学和天文学的区别吧
At least look up the difference between astrology and astronomy.
我只知道
Okay, alls I know is,
你现在这嘴脸可真是典型的摩羯座
is that you're being a real Capricorn right now.
太阳是围着地球转的
The sun revolves around the Earth,
不是围着你
and not you.
我真不敢相信我们订到了这家餐厅
I cannot believe we got into this restaurant.
就是说 你猜怎么着
I know. Oh, you know what?
脸书不就是为了在这种时候发照片炫耀的吗
Let's take a picture and use Facebook the way it was intended.
为了发现我们高中老友原来那么爱搞歧视
Oh, to find out how racist our high-school friends are?
不 为了让我们的亲朋好友
No, to make people in our lives
觉得过得不如我们好
feel worse about their lives.
先生们
Gentlemen.
二位的桌子马上就备好了
Your table's being set up right now.
好的
Okay.
-我的天 不 -怎么了
- Oh, my G- No. - ?What?
-那是卢克 -不 我们不能...
- Th-that's Luke. ?- No. We ca-
-我们不能坐在那 -我们不能坐他旁边
- We can't sit there. I'm s- - No, we can't sit next to --
能不能给我们换张桌
Can we have a-can we have a different table?
抱歉 今晚可不行
I'm sorry, not tonight.
如果你们不坐的话 还有十个人等着呢
If you guys don't want it, I have 10 other people who do.
好吧 你知道吗
Okay. You know what?
今晚本该是浪漫的一晚
Tonight was supposed to be a romantic night.
我不想看着他
?I-I don't want to watch him
饥渴地撩骚他这周的战利品
make his sweaty moves on his conquest of the week.
有些妹子还真上钩
And some of them buy it.
到底是哪的煤气大泄漏
Under what gas leak is
让他有这么多无脑女可找
he finding these brain-dead bimbos?
你听说他现在性格变得多糟糕吗
And have you heard how mean he's gotten?
那天他还说我们"阴险贼猫"呢
The other day, he called us "catty."
-他说我们阴险贼猫 -是的
- He called us catty? - ?Yeah.
他自己脑袋顶上那坨跟死猫似的
You sure he wasn't talking about the dead cat on his head
-还好意思说别人 -我的天
- he calls a haircut? - Oh, my --
你们好
Hey, guys!
卢克 真巧
?Hey, Luke! What a coincidence.
我觉得今晚我们能帮帮老爸和歌洛莉亚
I think it's nice that we're helping out
是件挺好的事
Dad and Gloria tonight.
我知道 我只是有点郁闷
I know. I'm just a little bummed
我们只能待在这照看乔
that we're stuck here, watching Joe,
我们本可以在复古跑车里亲热的
when we could be messing around in a Trans Am.
还是其实我们更上一层楼了
Or...did we just take it up a notch, huh?
我是性感保姆 孩子睡着了
I'm the foxy babysitter. The kid's asleep.
你是性感坏男孩
You are the foxy bad boy
拿着果酒偷偷过来
who sneaks over with some wine coolers...
真带劲儿
Oh, radical.
现在我六岁了 开始喜欢女孩子了
Now that I'm six, I like girls,
但我特爱两个女孩
but I love two girls --
小美人鱼和克莱尔
The Little Mermaid and Claire.
乔 你怎么起来了
Oh. Joe. W-What are you doing up?
克莱尔 这是我为你做的
Hello, Claire. I made this for you.
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
看 是情人节卡
Look, it's a Valentine.
是两只爱虫
It's two love bugs.
两只爱虫
Two love bugs.
第三只就是电灯泡
Three's a crowd.
你要喝点什么
Hey, how can I help you?
我是女商人吉吉·德拉罗卡
I am Gigi DeLaroca, businesswoman.
生活想将我压垮 但我却从中学到了智慧
Life has tried to break me, but it has only teach me.
所以你要不要喝点什么
So, you want a drink?
给这位女士来杯金巴利加苏打水
The lady will have Campari and soda.
你好 先生
Hello, sir.
我从没喝过那种饮料
I have never had that drink.
你无与伦比[金巴利谐音]
Well, no one "camparis" to you.
真聪明
Very clever.
我是女商人吉吉·德拉罗卡
I am Gigi DeLaroca, businesswoman.
我是拉尔夫·马塔多雷
I am Raoul Matadore.
这家酒店是我的 我能坐吗
I own this hotel. May I?
当然 马塔多雷先生
Of course, Mr. Matadore.
像《十一罗汉》里的安迪·加西亚一样
Like Andy Garcia in "Ocean's Eleven."
我觉得你没必要解释
I don't think you have to explain.
是的 你说
Right. Um, you talk.
不 我的意思是 谢谢
No, I mean, um... Thank you.
跟我说说你
Tell me about you.
你是做什么生意的
What business are you in? Bueno.
姑且说
Well, let's just say,
我是在夜晚工作的女人吧
I'm just a lady that works in the evening.
但不是什么男人都能一亲我芳泽
But I am not available to any man.
用魅力征服我吧 马塔多雷先生
So charm me, Mr. Matadore.
这间酒店
This hotel...
有世界上最高级的衣柜
has the finest closets in all the land.
我们有带灯的挂衣杆和无声衣柜门
We have lighted rods and soft-close doors.
我曾经嫁过一个
I was once married to a man
只会无休无止谈论衣柜的男人
that endlessly talked about closet.
你让我非常无聊
You're boring me very much.
好吧
Okay, well, um...
等我一下好吗
I need one secondo, huh?
我得处理下酒店事务
Hotel businesso, huh?
好的
Bueno.
我的天 服务员把菜单落在这了
Oh, my goodness. The waitress -- She left a menu here.
我在想我们是不是该点...
Now, I'm wondering if we should have got --
我的天 他的约会对象呢
Oh, my God! Where's his date?
你觉得他被放鸽子了吗
Do you think he got stood up?
-让我看看 -就在这
- Let me see that. - Right here.
太丢人了 我们该说些什么
It's so embarrassing. What do we even say?
菜单又不能隔音 没错 她放我鸽子了
They're not soundproof menus. Yeah. She's standing me up.
真搞不懂女人 你们说呢
Women are impossible, you know?
我们的确搞不懂
For us, they are.
有次我还真成功了
Well, now I made it work once,
她身后挂的帅哥罗伯·劳的海报也有功劳
although there was a-a Rob Lowe poster behind her.
要我说 忘了这姑娘吧
You know what? I say to heck to heck with this gal.
-去邂逅其他人 到酒吧去 -没错
- Get back out there, go to a bar! - ?Yes!
我赞成
I hear that.
-像你这样的小伙 一头秀发 -没错
- A guy like you, great head of hair... ?- Yep.
算了 我太郁闷了
Nah, I'm too depressed.
再说我已经提前付款了 我还是点餐吧
Besides, I prepaid for my meal. I guess I'll order.
无视我就好
Just forget I'm here.
话说回来 情人节快乐
Anyway... happy Valentine's Day.
-谢谢 -你看起来真帅气
- Thanks. - You look so handsome.
这太糟心了
This sucks.
真不敢相信我听你的劝玩起了这一套
I can't believe I let you talk me into doing this crap.
-快帮帮我 -没事的
- I need help! - It's okay.
在表象之下 不过还是你和你妻子
Underneath it all, it's just you and your wife.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
我都不知道当初是怎么追到她的
I don't know how I got her to begin with.
现在我开始觉得如果今晚不好好表现
And I'm starting to feel if I can't pull this off,
她会发觉她一开始是上我的当了
she's gonna figure out she got duped the first time.
让我先说句"谢谢"
Let me start by saying "Thank you"
谢谢你对我敞开心扉
for being so vulnerable with me.
我恨死你了
I hate you.
另外 我不是这事的专家
Also, I'm no expert at this,
但我认识一个专家
but I have a friend here who is.
我是克莱夫·比克斯比
Clive Bixby here.
要我帮你把今夜变得更性感吗
How can I make your night sexier?
如果我跟她玩不成角色扮演
If I can't role-play with her,
也不会跟你玩
I'm not doin' it with you.
随便吧 老爹
Whatevs, Daddio.
让我把电话还给菲利普
I'm gonna give the phone back to Philip.
是我菲尔
Phil here.
重点全在投入和自信上
Listen, it's all about commitment and confidence.
你扮成什么角色了
What's-what's your character?
拉尔夫·马塔多雷 酒店老板
Raoul Matadore, hotel owner,
像安迪·加西亚...
like Andy Garcia --
《十一罗汉》里的嘛 真适合你
In "Ocean's Eleven" -- I love this for you!
你用了表的那招吗
Did you go with the timepiece?
我就想着找机会 拿出表
Yeah, I thought at some moment, I'd pull it out,
往吧台上砸烂 对她说
smash it on the bar, and say,
"我想永远记得我坠入爱河的那一秒"
"I want to remember the exact moment I fell in love."
-我就是个白痴 -你不是
- I'm an idiot! - ?No.
我沉默是因为我要捡起惊掉的下巴
That silence is me picking my jaw up off the floor.
我们还在学走路 你已经在飞了 大师
We're all walking, and you're flying, mister.
真的吗 你真这么觉得
Seriously? You think so?
我1000%觉得 但最好还是问高手
1,000%! But don't take it from me.
现在又是克莱夫
Clive again.
马塔多雷先生 我脱高领衫向你致敬
Mr. Matadore, I tip my turtleneck to ya.
还在吗
Hello?
好啦 不许偷看
All right, no peeking.
我不偷看
Oh, no peeking.
希望你不会失望
I hope you're not disappointed.
天啊 好美
Wow! It's so pretty!
你知道还有什么很美吗
You know what else is pretty?
你讨厌啦
Oh! Stop.
我本来是要说"金星"
Well, I was going to say "Venus."
但行吧 就夸你美
But sure, let's go with you.
来吧 来看看
Come on, have a look.
不是这样
Nope.
好吧
Oh! Okay.
是新月 所以今晚特别适合
Yeah, there's a new moon, so it's the perfect night
观测微弱的星团
to observe faint star clusters.
而 而在正中央
?And -- And right in the middle,
有一颗我所发现的变星
there's a variable star that I discovered.
就在一个白矮星[白侏儒]旁
It's right next to a white dwarf.
现在好像不能用这种词汇称呼人家了
Oh, I don't think you're allowed to say that anymore.
是啊 这年代说话得很小心
Yes, tricky times we live in.
这真是太酷炫了
Wow, this is so cool.
是啊 你想像一下这个
Right. Have a -- Have a think about this --
有个理论说整个宇宙大到
There is a theory that suggests the universe is so large
世上所有能发生的事情 全都正在发生
that everything that can happen is happening all the time.
你抽大麻吗
Do you smoke weed?
不啊
Oh. No.
抱歉 我有一点太着迷宇宙
Sor-- Sorry, I'm a little obsessed with space.
我在10岁时造了人生第一个多布森望远镜
I-I built my first Dobsonian telescope when I was 10.
你造了望远镜吗
You made a telescope?
我唯一做过的东西就是送我妈的烟灰缸
The only thing I've ever made was an ashtray for my mom
上面还写着"请在这里摩擦你的屁股"
that says, "Rub your butt here."
就是在说烟屁股
Oh, like cigarette butt.
是的
Yeah.
你8月27号有安排了吗
What are you doing next August 27th
大概晚上8点
8:00 P.M.?
我不知道啊 怎么了
I have no idea. Why?
太空总署要为我做的防辐射层给我颁奖
NASA is giving me an award for a radiation shield,
-而... -太空总署要给你颁奖吗
- and -- ?NASA's giving you an award?
我需要带个伴 你别有压力啊
I need a date. There's no pressure.
不过我做的东西救了一群宇航员的性命呢
But it saved the lives of a bunch of astronauts.
你好有成就啊
Wow, you've done a lot.
我相信你也有不少
Well, I'm -- I'm sure you've had
属于你的成就吧
your share of accomplishments.
是啊 当然啦
Oh, yeah! Yeah, of course.
我想想啊 有一个...
Let's see. There was, um...
大学...
college...
不 不 这话题
Nope. Nope. That is a --
通向了一条死路
that is a bad road.
好吧 在我的工作上...
Well, uh, uh, okay, so professionally,
我有涉猎... 比如...
I've been kind of sort of dabbling in, like,
很多不同的... 算了
a lot of different -- Pass.
我有一次坐飞机
Um...I-I-I-I once flew
坐在杀手乐团的贝斯手旁边呢
next to the bass player of The Killers.
好啦 其实好像只是长得像的人
Uh, you know, it just kind of looked like him.
这里有洗手间吗
Is there a bathroom?
帮我拿着 我自己去找找
Here, I'm just gonna find it myself.
没什么 我没事 我很好
No big deal. I'm fine. I'm -- I'm great.
我...
I...
最近有跟新的人交往吗
So, are you seeing anybody new?
没有 我今年都没给我妈做情人节卡片呢
No, I didn't even make my mom a Valentine's card this year.
我问你有没有跟人交往
It's alarming that I asked about dating,
而你直接说到你妈 这样好吗
and you went right to your mother.
你好
Hello?
艾丽克斯 我是费诺曼教授
Alex, it's Professor Fennerman.
很抱歉在情人节打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you on Valentine's.
没事的
Uh, it's okay. Uh...
海莉有联系你吗
Have you heard from Haley?
她不是跟你在一起吗
Isn't she with you?
本来是啊 但她突然就跑掉了
She was, and... then she suddenly ran off.
我想... 我好像让她无聊到
I think -- I think I may have bored her
受不了逃跑了
to the point of fleeing.
你怎么可能会让人无聊呢
You could never bore anyone.
你知道谁才是真无聊吗 舍费尔教授
You know who's boring? Professor Schaeffer.
同意 他无聊到要死
Agreed. He's insufferable.
总是嘴上叨叨个没完
He never stops droning on.
他就像是宇宙微波背景辐射一样
He's like the cosmic microwave background radiation.
因为他是永远都弄不走的持续噪声
Because he's the constant noise you can't get rid of!
太好了 今晚终于有人能懂我说的话了
Thank God somebody gets me tonight.
我觉得或许带她来天文台
You know, I think it might have been a bad idea,
并不是什么好主意
bringing her to the observatory.
或许我应该把目光放在
I probably should have set my sights on someone
跟我更有共同话题的姑娘身上
with whom I have more in common.
你懂我意思吗
Do you know what I mean?
我应该懂吧
I...think I do?
好了 我打算再多等一会
Anyway, I think I'll wait here a little longer,
看一会儿星星 以防她突然出现
take in the stars, just in case she shows up.
或许她会出现的
Maybe she will.
谢了 艾丽克斯
Thanks, Alex.
天啊
Oh, my God.
-怎么了 -海莉弃他而去了
- What? - ?Haley blew him off.
他好像想要我去天文台那里陪他
I think he wants me to come to the observatory to be with him.
你对他有感觉啊
You have feelings for this guy?
谁不会对他有感觉啊
Who wouldn't?!
你知道想找到一个
I mean, do you know how hard it is
有颜值的天才有多难吗
to find a good-looking genius?
除了他 就只剩打扮一下后的我了
There's him, and when I put in a little effort, me!
那就去吧
Then go.
我这就去
I will.
你就去吧 我也要去
Yeah, you will, a-and I'm gonna make
给我妈做一张情人节卡片
a Valentine for my mom.
这两件事不一样好吗
They're not the same!
好 先打开我的
Okay, open -- open mine first.
这个形状是和服
Oh. ?It's -- It's a kimono.
我上了网上的折纸课
I took an online origami class.
好吧
Okay.
是俳句
It's a haiku. ?
"友爱人丈夫
"Friend, lover, husband.
人生从见你开始
My life started when we met.
你是我所有"
You're my everything."
你真的是
Aww. ?You are.
来看看你给我写了什么
Ooh, let's see what you wrote in yours.
是协力脚踏车
Aww. It's a tandem bicycle.
真是有爱
Yeah. ?It's so cute.
"情节快乐
"Happy V-Day.
爱你 米"
Love, M."
本以为我的妞够冷血了呢
And I thought my date was cold.
怎么 小卡知道我意思[毒]
What? No. Cam knows what I mean.
小卡知道你毒吗
Cam knows you are mean?
你对今晚的菜单流露出的感情
You were more effusive about tonight's menu
都比给我的卡片多
than you were in my card.
"熔岩巧克力蛋糕看起来又骚气又美味"
"The molten chocolate cake looks slutty and delicious."
你也这么说我会死啊
Would it kill you to say that about me?
什么鬼 阿曼达有来这里
What the hell? Amanda was here.
你们贴在脸书上的照片
This picture you posted on Facebook --
她就在你们背后 她为什么就走了呢
She's right behind you. Why would she just leave?
今晚本该是浪漫的一晚
Tonight was supposed to be a romantic night.
我不想看着他饥渴地撩骚
I don't want to watch Luke make his sweaty moves
他这周的战利品
on his conquest of the week.
有些妹子还真上钩
Yeah, and some of them buy it.
到底是哪的煤气大泄露
Under what gas leak is
让他有这么多无脑女可找
he finding these brain-dead bimbos?
我知道发生了什么
I know what happened.
她走进店里 第一次看到我本人
She walked in, saw me for the first time,
觉得我长得很丑
and thought I was hideous.
我最近的发型真是怎么弄都弄不好
I've really been struggling with my hair lately.
别 才没有 你发型好看死了
No, no, stop it. You have great hair.
席娜·伊斯顿留这发型好看 你也能留得好看
If it worked for Sheena Easton, it can work for you.
我们互通短信了这么长时间
We spent all this time texting.
我还以为我们真的心心相印
I thought we had a real connection,
就真的很理解彼此
like, really got each other.
我们不忍心任他埋怨自己
We couldn't let him blame himself.
他知道后... 还接受得挺好
But, uh...he took it pretty well.
你们俩阴险贼猫可真损
You catty bitches!
卢克 我们爱你 但自从你进入青春期
Luke, we love you, but ever since you hit puberty,
-你就有点... 讨人厌 -讨人厌
- you've been... a little disgusting. - A little disgusting.
这还用你们说啊
Don't you think I know that?!
她不就是我扭转乾坤的机会吗
She was my chance to turn it around.
好 这样吧 打给她
Okay, you know what? Call her.
我们跟她讲讲 帮你把整件事解释一下
We'll get on the phone, we'll clear the whole thing up.
我打给她了 她不接电话
I called her. She's not picking up.
我们现在就去她家
We're going to her apartment.
我们惹的祸 我们得弥补
We messed this up, we'll fix it.
在蛋糕上之前就走吗
Before the cake arrives?
我一整晚都等着把脸埋进蛋糕里了
I've been wanting to bury my face in that all night long.
你听不到你对它多浪漫吗
How can you not hear this?
好了 乔 时间晚了
Okay, Joey, it's getting late.
是时候该让你上床睡觉了
It's time to get you up to bed.
你能帮我看一眼房间有没有怪兽吗
Can you do a quick monster check first?
可以 没问题
Yes, I can.
菲尔 我睡觉不能没有小熊陪
Phil, I can't sleep without my teddy bear,
我把它忘在我小拖车上了
and I left him in my wagon.
你能去帮我拿来吗 我怕黑
Can you get him? I'm afraid of the dark.
没问题 小兄弟
You got it, buddy.
乔 你在干嘛
Joe? What are you doing?
打开门
Open the door.
弗汉希欧·乔瑟夫·普里契特
Fulgencio Joseph Pritchett!
把门打开
Open the door!
年轻人 你马上开门让我进来
You let me in right now, young man.
你不能这样 乔
Not cool, Joe!
乔 这音乐是怎么回事
Joe, what is going on with this music?
我的天啊
My God.
菲尔去哪里了
Oh. Where's Phil?
谁知道那家伙啊
Who knows what that guy?
亲爱的 怎么回事
Honey, what happened?
小情圣把我锁外面了
Mini Casanova locked me out.
什么 够了
What? That is enough.
乔 你就是个小孩
Joe, you are a little boy,
你现在立刻去睡觉
and you're going to bed right now.
你是个烂情人
You're a bad Valentine!
惨了
Oh, no.
感觉就像电影《早餐俱乐部》中
I feel like the rest of the Breakfast Club
其他人发现贾德·尼尔森的角色
when they realized Judd Nelson was
没有他们想象中那么硬气时那样...
more vulnerable than they thought. ?I...
我在伊比沙岛的那间旅馆是我的最爱
My hotel in Ibiza was my favorite.
当年我们一起玩的人有泰利·萨瓦拉斯
I used to hang out with Telly Savalas,
莱尔·瓦戈纳[都是老牌明星]
Lyle Waggoner,
但眼前的风景
but the scenery here
更让我爱不释手
makes me like this one mucho more.
你不需要靠
You don't have to impress me
有钱或是扯名人来引起我兴趣 是名人吧
with money or name-dropping, I think.
我喜欢你
I like you.
不要告诉我的鸨母
Don't tell this to my madam,
但我不能收你任何钱
but I cannot accept any money from you.
抱歉 女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
我能跟你借一步说话吗
Can I talk with you for a moment?
怎么啦
Yes?
我得请您离开
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave now.
我们旅馆的老板
The hotel owner is very strict
对您这行的女性十分严格
about women who do what you do.
你要带我去个房间
Ooh, you're gonna take me to a room
然后你们旅馆老板要给我来一场
where the hotel owner is going to give me
十分凶悍又性感的"教训"吗
a very tough, sexy talking to?
不是 您得离开 不然我们要叫警察了
No, you're gonna leave, or we're gonna call the police.
-行啊 你叫警察吧 -歌洛莉亚
- Yes, call the police. - Gloria --
我是个很不乖的"坏女孩"
I've been a very, very bad girl.
这不是角色扮演的一部分
This is not a part of it.
先生 她不是妓女
Sir, she is not a prostitute.
她是我老婆
This is my wife.
你们这些人都这么说
That's what they all say.
这边请
Please.
是啦 要我我估计也这么说
Yep, that's probably what I would've said.
她在那里 琪柯妮
Here she is. Ciconi.
你来干嘛
What do you want?
-你好啊 -她来了
- Oh, hi! - Here she is.
她比照片上还漂亮
You're actually hotter than your picture.
来 我们来谈 你好 我们...
You know, let us talk. Hi! So, we're --
-我们是卢克的舅舅们 -我们是卢克的舅舅
- we're Luke's uncles. - We're Luke's uncles.
你们是他舅舅吗
You're his uncles?
你们说他饥渴地撩骚无脑女吗
And you said he put sweaty moves on brain-dead bimbos?
好吧 你们没说那么详细
Okay, hadn't heard the specifics.
好啦 是... 是这样啦
Okay, you know -- you know what?
我们说这些话不是真心的
We d-- We didn't mean any of that.
我们是同性恋 同性恋特毒舌
We're gay, and gays are snarky.
我们文化就这样
It's a cultural thing.
就像比方说 你是意大利人吧
You know how, like, you're Italian?
意大利人说话手势特别多 对吧
Italians talk a lot with their hands, right
而且跟其他天主教徒比
and are much looser
你们也比较放荡...
than one would imagine for Catholics.
够了 让我来说
Okay, okay. Let me talk right now.
阿曼达 卢克是很棒的小伙
Okay, Amanda, Luke's an amazing guy.
我为什么要信你现在的解释
Why would I believe what you're saying now
而不是你们之前说的话
and not what you said before?
我不知道 我真不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
或许我们之前只是故意毒舌抬杠
You know, maybe we were just being snarky
因为我们很嫉妒你们俩
because we were jealous of you guys. Yeah.
看到卢克穿得整整齐齐
I mean, seeing Luke all dressed up,
准备好要初次约会...
getting ready for a first date, the --
小年轻陷入爱河的那种兴奋感
the excitement of being young and in love.
别太过头
Mm. ?Easy.
我还记得我初次见到小卡的画面
I-I remember when I first met Cam --
-我是小卡 -他是小卡
- I'm Cam. - This is Cam.
我当时就知道我见到了
I knew I had met the person
我想要共度余生的人
I was gonna spend the rest of my life with.
我也想要这个 一段感情
That's what I want, too -- a relationship,
有一个会陪在我身旁的人
someone who's gonna be there for me.
卢克也是这个感觉
Luke feels the same way.
他是个准备好要全身心投入的小伙
I mean, this is a guy who is ready for commitment.
我们只是互通短信过
We've really only texted.
当我说
Okay, well, when I say --
当我说请你给卢克一个机会
when I say to give Luke a chance,
是因为我知道这对你会有多重要
it's because I-I know what's at stake for you.
你觉得你们现在已经很棒了吗
I-I mean, you think it's amazing now?
你都想象不到你们发展下去会变多赞
You can't even imagine what it could grow into.
如果你们能有哪怕万分之一的机会
If you guys have even the smallest chance
得到我们之间的感情 你就必需得去尝试啊
of having what we have... you have to go for it.
天啊 米奇尔
Oh, my God, Mitchell.
这才是我一直想要的情人节卡片啊
That is the Valentine's Day card I've always wanted.
真是太甜蜜了
That was sweet.
但卢克已经跑了
But Luke's gone.
一直开 开到你听到有派对再停
Drive until you hear a party.
好啦 亲爱的 祝你好运吧
Okay. Well, you know what? Good luck, honey.
-再见 -你好好保重
- Bye, then. - Yeah, take care.
你看 我们有同样的住址
You see, we have the same address
还有同样的姓
and the same last name.
我只是在扮演成一个妓女
I was just pretending to be a prostitute
因为我丈夫对电影《柳巷芳草》有情节
because my husband has a thing for Jane Fonda in "Klute."
女主身材要命了
The body was crazy,
但可惜 里面的官僚斗争也是
unfortunately, so were the politics.
好吧 你们没有违反我们旅馆的任何规定
Well, I guess you didn't do anything wrong by hotel rules,
但根据我个人的信仰来说
but based on my personal belief system --
没打算要听你的意见 谢谢
We're not looking for any input. Thank you.
我真是不敢相信我听了菲尔的情场建议
I can't believe I took romantic advice from Phil,
一个我起码看他穿过三次皮短裤的成年男子
a grown man I've seen in lederhosen at least three times.
是菲尔叫你搞角色扮演的吗
Phil told you to do the role play?
对啊 他说你今早不高兴
Yeah, he said you were mad this morning
因为我总是在这种大日子掉链子
because I always drop the ball on days like this.
我不是生你气
I wasn't mad at you.
我是在气乔
I was mad at Joe
他没给我做情人节卡片
because he didn't make me a Valentine.
所以你的六岁儿子
So your 6-year-old kid
没给你做卡片 你就生气到
doesn't give you a card, you get so mad,
用撬胎棒砸穿挡风玻璃
you throw a tire iron through the windshield.
生气的原因应该是更深层的吧
It's got to be deeper than that.
是曼尼 这也是他第一次
Manny, for the first time ever,
没给我情人节卡片
didn't make me a Valentine's, either.
这不是更深层
That's not deeper.
这是同一件有毛病的事乘二
That's just doubling down on the same disturbing thing.
有毛病
Disturbing?
当曼尼五岁的时候
When Manny was 5 years old,
她说他会永远当我的情人
he told me that he would forever be my Valentine's.
他许下的约定 我怎可被遗忘
Promises were made. I will not be ignored!
好啦 听起来是挺怪的
Okay, yeah. That sounded weird.
但重点是我知道
But the point is that I know
你不擅长搞这些浪漫的招数
that you're not good at romantic things,
所以我无所谓
and I'm fine with it.
你不能这么轻易放过我啊
Don't let me off the hook.
如果我做得更好
If I did more,
你就不用依靠你两个儿子来得到浪漫了
you wouldn't depend on your kids for those things.
要说我今晚
And if I learned anything
试图泡你时学到了什么
from trying to pick you up tonight,
那就是我当年能泡到你真是走大运了
it's how lucky I was to get you in the first place.
我得做得更好
I've got to do better.
我也不觉得世上会有
And I didn't think anyone
比拉尔夫·马塔多雷更性感的男人了
could get any sexier than Raoul Matadore.
我想永远记得
I want to remember the exact moment
我重新坠入爱河的那一秒
I fell in love with you all over again.
你他妈干嘛呢
What the hell have you done?
那是我爸爸的表
That was my father's watch!
可怜的乔
Poor little Joe.
你没觉得我有故意吊着他吧
You don't think I led him on, do you?
不 不对
No, no.
我不能这样
I am not doing this.
女人总是怪是不是自己的问题
Women always blame themselves.
抱歉 乔 我没欠你什么
Well, I'm sorry, Joe. I don't owe you anything.
这样吧 我想还是我来处理吧
You know what? I-I think I'll handle this.
小家伙
Hey, buddy.
你也要来骂我吗
Are you gonna yell at me, too?
听我说
Listen.
克莱尔凶你的原因是因为
The reason Claire was yelling at you
她想要保护我的感受
was to protect my feelings.
她知道我根本比不上你
She knows I can't compete with you,
所以呢...
which is, um...
我想请你帮我一个大忙
which is why I have to ask you a really big favor.
你能去跟别的女生好吗
Can you pick another girl?
像你这样 什么女生都会喜欢你
I mean, you can have anyone you want,
但我只有克莱尔了
but... Claire's all I've got.
失去她 我就失去了一切
I'd be lost without her.
我自己都不知道我当初怎么泡到她的
I don't even know how I got her in the first place.
你的确挺傻的
You are pretty silly.
那你怎么说
What do you say?
爷们之间的约定 你愿意收手吗
Dude to dude, will you back off?
好吧
Okay.
海莉有在跟人交往吗
Is Haley seeing anyone?
你悠着点
Easy.
我怎么回到阿尔文身边的 我也不知道
How'd I get back to Arvin? I don't know.
我本来是在找停车场
I was just looking for the parking lot
结果遇到了一个岔路
when I came to a fork in the path.
如果我选了另一条
Had I taken the other path,
或许我已经上了我的车回家了
I would've just gotten in my car and gone home.
可是呢...
Instead...
你回来啦
You came back!
靠 还真是
Damn it, I did!
你为什么跑掉啊 我做什么了
Why did you run off? What did I do?
你什么都做到了 而我一事无成
Everything. And I've done nothing.
我感觉自己就是个废柴
I-I feel like a loser.
你觉得自己是废柴吗
You feel like a loser?
你觉得我为什么这么讨人厌在自卖自夸呢
Why do you think I went on about myself so appallingly?
快看我
Ooh, look at me.
我在应用臭屁学领域
I won the Von Snootington Award
赢得了"炊扭比"大奖呢
for Applied Astro-Doofinomics.
你又赢了一个奖吗 这怎么安慰到我了
You won another award? How is this helping?
海莉 我喜欢你
Haley...I like you.
你的强大与难以对付
You are formidable in a way that's...
与别人好不一样 令我斗志十足
that's different and exciting to me.
我也是这感觉
Yeah, well, same,
但感觉就是不合理啊
but it just doesn't make sense.
我就喜欢不合理的事情
I love things that don't make sense.
这是我的强项
That's my gig. ?
我们一起来把它理理顺吧
Let's figure this out together.
来嘛
Come on.
我能怎么做
What can I do?
这挺有帮助
That helps.
一想到如果我走了另一边
Oh, it's so weird to think that if I had taken another path,
我现在可能已经到家了就好怪
I could be heading home right now.
等等 这就像你之前说的一样
Wait a minute. It's like what you said before.
在另一个不同的宇宙 你可能跟别人在一起了
In a different universe, you could be with someone else.
我们... 我们能换首歌吗
Um, could we... could we change this song?
这歌的氛围有点破坏我蓝调的做爱风格
The poppy cadence is throwing off my more bluesy lovemaking style.
你们都不敲门的吗
Don't you ever knock?!
这是我的卧室
This is my bedroom!
我真不敢相信这种事又发生了一次
I can't believe this is happening again!
又发生吗
Again?
我真希望我当时被逮捕走了
I wish I had gotten arrested!
妈 你在哪
Mom, where are you?
我给你做了张情人节卡...
I made you a Valen...
我不在的这些时候 你们都在搞什么鬼啊
What kind of freak show goes on here when I'm not around?